[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "Which is the world's largest iceland?",
    "answers": [
      "Icland",
      "Ireland",
      "Gotland",
      "Greenland"
    ],
    "correct": "Greenland"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What does PHP stand for?",
    "answers": [
      "Hypertext Pre-processor",
      "Personal HTML Pages",
      "Professional HTML Parser",
      "Pre-processing Hypertext Processing-engine"
    ],
    "correct": "Hypertext Pre-processor"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the number of decimals in π?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "3.14",
      "3.14 trillion",
      "Technically infinite"
    ],
    "correct": "Technically infinite"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which Swedish bird rules the browser?",
    "answers": [
      "Måsvingen",
      "Hakparamesen",
      "DOMHerren",
      "Kokokol"
    ],
    "correct": "DOMHerren"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the result of: Array(16).join('lol' - 2) + ' Batman!';",
    "answers": [
      "False",
      "lol",
      "Error",
      "NaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaN Batman!"
    ],
    "correct": "NaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaNNaN Batman!"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which of the following is the oldest javascript framework?",
    "answers": [
      "React",
      "Angular",
      "Vue",
      "Next.js"
    ],
    "correct": "Angular"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "In javscript, what doas \"NaN === NaN\" equal to?",
    "answers": [
      "false",
      "NaN",
      "Error",
      "true"
    ],
    "correct": "false"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "How many kilograms of coffee does the average swede consume per year?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "3",
      "21"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What was JavaScript previously called?",
    "answers": [
      "LiveScript",
      "CoffeeScript",
      "WebScript",
      "Gecko"
    ],
    "correct": "LiveScript"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a JavaScript library?",
    "answers": [
      "MooTools",
      "Mocha",
      "Knockout.js",
      "Vanilla.js"
    ],
    "correct": "Vanilla.js"
  }
]
